This is a rip and review [music] of
Topps Chrome update 2526. If you want to
skip directly to the rip, go [music]
right here. This is the very first year
of Topps Chrome update in basketball.
We've got a lot of new inserts that
[music] they didn't have before. They're
introducing now in the first time we've
had it. If you'd like to know all the
box configurations, [music] you can
check them out here. Take a screenshot.
Save it for later. Let's go over the
most common inserts. Some that you might
see in pretty [music] much every single
box that you open. So, you got power
players, stratospheric stars, clutch
city, fortune [music] 15, clutch gene,
moment in time. Now, let's move on to
the more rare inserts. Not the most rare
inserts, but definitely some [music] you
want to keep in your collection if you
find some. The first one is no limit for
players that truly have no limit. It's a
10-card checklist you can find in
[music] one in every 39 hobby packs.
Now, the next one we've got up is
captains, which is a little misleading
because [music] not every one in the
checklist is a captain, but they do
command respect on the court. This is a
20-player checklist that you'll find one
[music] in every 409 packs. So, me
personally, I've always loved the look
of this card. It was always a big chase
in baseball, and now we finally have it
here in basketball. [music] That is
shadow edge, and you'll find that in one
in every 545 packs. [music] Back again,
we've got radiating rookies, and of
course, you've guessed it, this is where
you'll find your rookies. One in [music]
every 545 packs, and it's a 15-person
checklist. Now, the next one up,
celebration. This is one you're going to
find [music] in one in every 570 packs,
a 15-player checklist, [music] and as
you can tell by this card, it looks like
a party. Now, let's move on to the most
rare cards. Now, if you find something
like this, you [music] know you got
something good. Now, one chase that we
all know and love is the almighty helix.
This is a beautiful card design that
collectors are going to love and are
going to chase. But, [music] the chase
is on because you only got them in one
in every 3,744
packs. This is a 20-person checklist.
Now, this next one we're going to talk
about, it's a base variation, but it's
so rare that it's definitely worth
talking about, and that is [music] denim
tears. Now, because it's base, there
will be 200 variations, but still super
hard to find, one in every 6,054 [music]
packs. Outside of patches and autos,
this is going to be your biggest chase,
and that is alter egos. Not only are
they extremely [music] rare, the artwork
is amazing. The way they take the
player's personality and turn it into an
illustration, top tier. Now, this
[music] next one might be a little bit
controversial, but like it or love it,
we've got something that's extremely
rare. That is [music] the minion
fractor. Now, this is an extremely rare
hit. I'm talking one out of every 12,456
packs. This is only a five player
checklist. They made sure to only
reserve these for the guys that are at
the top of their game, the ones that
mean you want to chase. Now, the [music]
first autos we'll talk about are Topps
Chrome autographs. Extremely long
checklist. If the player signs in Topps,
you can [music] see them here. Now, they
are the most common autos that you will
find in a guaranteed auto box, but if
it's a great player, it's still got to
be a fan- tastic hit. Now, these autos
you will find one [music] in every 141
packs. Now, the next one we've got is
the rookie autographs lava lamp. Now,
[music] extremely long checklist, but
again, this will only be reserved for
rookies, and you'll find these in every
295 packs. [music] Now, before we get to
our biggest chases in the product, we've
got to mention our special guest.
[music] The two big names we're talking
about, Spike Lee and Druski. Y'all know
Spike Lee, one of the biggest fans of
the New York Knicks.
>> [music]
>> And Druski, you've been seeing him poke
around the hobby lately. Great to have
them both in the set. Now, for Druski,
you're going to find his auto in one in
every 80,960
packs. [music] Now, for Spike Lee's
auto, it's a lot more rare to find. I'm
talking about one in every 138,789
packs. Now, here comes the biggest
[music] chase in the hobby. That's
right, I'm talking about the debut
patch. [music] If you don't know, guys,
this is a patch that literally was used
in the player's very first game, taken
directly from the jersey and put into a
card that we're going to go chase. If
you weren't aware guys, the debut patch
is the biggest chase that is [music]
coming to the hobby since Topps has
taken over the license of basketball.
Just the fact that [music] this product
has the debut patch in it makes it so
much more enticing for collectors like
you and I. All right guys, without
further ado, let's get into the product.
Nice design, Cooper and Wemby on the
front. Either one of these guys would be
amazing right now.
All right, let's see.
First look.
Oh, I've got something colorful here in
the back.
Chris Middleton, Jalen Brunson.
Naz Reid Marshall.
How about already a power players of
Karl Malone on the Jazz? Beautiful card
right there. Definitely seems like an
old school design which I enjoy a lot.
Hopefully you collect his will as well.
Nice little insert right there.
Let's see what we got.
Looks like they uh
refractor here.
Bronny for the Hawks, Jalen Johnson.
Nice refractor.
Jakub Jonas, Jalen Green. There's
another power players for Evan Mobley
DPOY. Thomas Ober rookie.
Nice Evan Mobley power players.
Come on, let's find something good.
There's a uh
Hugo Gonzalez.
Liam McNeely, Kelly Oubre.
Dame time, going back to the Blazers. I
love that. Got the Blazers jersey on.
Back home to the Blazers in Portland.
Like the design on these, man.
But now I got to see one of these
exclusives. I want to see something for
that update we'll give us.
There's one.
There's a new one, and there's Dillon
Harper.
On the moment in time. That's a very
cool picture right there. Giving us
literally the exact moment in time, as
you see has a little recording there,
which shows you the camera action. I
love that with the crowd in the back.
Very cool design.
Chazz Lanier
and Trey Murphy.
Where's Wemby? Where's Scoot?
Where's Wemby? Where's Scoot? Where's
LeBron?
How crazy is it, guys, if we pull this a
debut patch right here?
Cavaliers, Jarrett Allen.
Hometown hero from Austin, Texas.
I'm from Austin, Texas.
Come on.
I think I see redemption.
Classic design. Well, there's Scooper
slamming it down, man. That's an updated
card, for sure. I didn't see that design
before. I love that. Scooper going
crazy.
Uh, we have
Bronny James auto to 99. That's a
gorgeous card right there. The true
green.
True green, not geometric like you would
see in sapphire. It's a gorgeous card
right there. On-card auto
of Bronny James. That's one of the autos
you'll see, guys. That's one of the
opportunities you'll find. That true
green, the 99.
Gorgeous card.
That should be our auto in the box, but
you never know with Top Opps, you just
might find another.
Derrick White
and Javon Small.
Very nice-looking cards. Obviously look
the same as they did before with the uh
Topps Chrome.
Um
with some updates to the jerseys and the
pictures. There's Sabonis. Celtics. Give
me Jason Tatum. There we go, to 299.
222. Angel numbers.
Come on, let's see.
Maybe we get lucky with the second auto.
You never know.
Got to keep hunting.
Very nice one right here. Buddy Hield.
Jaren Jackson Jr. and
Fortune 15 Donovan Mitchell.
That's one of the inserts that we were
talking about, guys. There's a Fortune
15.
Donny Mitch. Spider.
Oh, we do have uh
activators for Brandon Brandon Miller.
Kevin Garnett.
Another Cavaliers. How about Lonzo Ball
99?
That's a little bit different. As you
guys see the difference between the 99s,
this is a true green in 99, and this
one's going to be your wave, I believe.
Come on.
I got to see something crazy. Got to see
something crazy. Back to Dillon Harper.
Devin Booker and Andrew Wiggins on the
refractor.
Shai Gilgeous-Alexander, Bobby Portis,
and there's another moment in time Luka
Dončić.
I'm sure he drained that. Rudy, I'm
sorry, man.
Bennedict Mathurin. Here comes another
refractor. Give me Jeremiah Fears. How
about zero fears refractor rookie?
Great player right there.
Another Activators it looks like. How
about LeBron with a very cool design
right there? I mean, he must have jammed
it down.
And there's LaMelo Ball.
Now moving on to the Timberwolves.
It's going to be a fun fun game to see a
fun uh series to see with him and
Ant-Man for sure.
Alex Caruso back-to-back OKC OG Anunoby
the Hand of God.
And there's your Clutch Gene.
JayDub.
Clutch Genes making their way back.
Making their way back to Tops.
Evan Mobley, Larry Bird.
AR-15.
And there's Derrick White.
Very similar to the last card we just
showed you guys. There's the wave again,
but there's non-numbered wave. Last
three packs. Let's see what we can get.
Con Knippel.
T.J. McConnell.
Naz Reid.
Shareef Abdur-Rahim.
Got an insert here.
That's nice.
Stratospheric Stars James Harden. That's
a really cool looking card there.
Stratospheric Stars. Now you know what
it looks like and that's definitely one
of these Stratospheric Stars. I mean, he
was putting up Stratospheric numbers at
one point. Last pack mojo. Let's see
what we can do, squad.
Another insert to end this off.
Let's get a good look at it.
I like it. Tyrese Haliburton.
On the go time. It's go time, baby.
Probably not the best box, which just
means [music] I gave you an opportunity
to go get it yourself, right? Now if you
did skip to the rip, just make sure you
go back to the beginning. We do give you
guys some information about some of the
cards and some of the inserts that we
may not have seen here during the rip.
Make sure you guys like, comment, and
subscribe. I mean, we really want to
hear from you. Is there anything that
you're excited about that we didn't
speak [music] about? Or do you share the
same love with some of the cards that
you see here that we spoke about today?
[music] Until next time, thank you guys
so much for ripping with us, and I hope
you have an amazing time [music] ripping
this product.